This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander.
A hero!
This is my story!
Let's go.
I've never seen my dreams.
It's not so far.
I've never seen it.
I was always hoping that you were me.
I've never been able to.
I'm going to be you.
I'm going to be the light of this world.
I'll be the light of the future.
Hey, there's something that
I've been wanting to ask you.
Did Yachiho do any
training to prep for today?
Anything you can tell me would be great.
Wake up!
Yachiho hasn't been acting
any different than usual.
Actually, she's been in a good mood.
Guess that means she
doesn't expect much, Himari.
Is everyone ready?
Now let the first match begin! Bacon!
Don't say I didn't warn you.
You won't last a second again.
Where the hell did that come from?
Golden Hour!
The line, five seconds!
Bacon!
She's tired.
We planned ahead in case we couldn't
beat her with a single blow.
Let's stick to our strategy!
A gun modified for use in Mato.
I knew that would be her main weapon.
Leaping into the air where she's
a sitting duck was a dumb move.
When she starts coming down, I'll
use Golden Hour to freeze time.
And blast her!
Do it now!
Ah!
Time for golden hour!
Rewind five seconds!
An airborne kick to gain momentum?
She really cut it close with that one.
But if I activate my
ability sooner than planned,
they'll be moving into my
attack range when I freeze time!
Golden hour!
Freeze for five seconds!
No, where did it go?
You're out of range.
She's changing tactics on me.
Yes, we made her waste her ability.
Stand your ground and stick to the plan.
Roger that.
Whoa, incredible.
Faster than his fading bullet!
Is Himari trying to confuse her opponent?
She's running circles around Yachi-ho!
I can feel it in my bones.
I can feel how desperately
Himari wants to win.
As for my ultimate goal...
I want to be a hero like the commander.
I feel like I'll become a better version
of myself if I can beat Yachi-ho.
I have to help her win!
I'll make sure of it!
Yeah, you got this!
It's almost like I'm seeing devil!
Do it!
You petulant little brat! Nice.
We threw her off balance.
Just like we planned they certainly
came prepared didn't they?
It's shaping up to be a good match.
Do you think that Yachiho
will be okay I assumed
his servitude was reserved
exclusively for Kyo?
But it seems he's capable of devoting
himself to a new master too interesting.
This man I mean Yuki he's busting his
ass for me more than I expected him to.
I'll have to apologize for
giving him such a hard time.
That's just another reason why
I've got to destroy Yachi-ho!
Golden Hour can't be
activated instantaneously.
The trigger is that dumb pose of hers.
So depending on our position
when she starts to move,
it's our cue to either attack or retreat.
And we can tell whether or not she already
used her ability based on her behavior.
If she's tired all of a sudden,
it's proof that she rewound time.
Then we change things up and
hightail it out of there.
It's a drain on her energy so
she can only use her ability
a few more times at best if
we can make her waste it.
We're guaranteed to win!
I bet that's exactly what he
Maria is thinking right now.
I figured out her logic and her
strategy I'll drag her back home
and make her life a living hell
Guess it's time to play my trap card!
Feel the power of your big sister!
She's going to freeze time,
but we're safe at this!
Prime time!
Freeze for ten seconds!
If it were only five, she'd
be out of my attack range.
But with a ten-second head
start, she can't escape!
What just happened?
Himani turned up the heat, but
now she's down for the count!
Prime time!
By striking the ultimate pose, I double
the amount of time I can control.
The only downside was that it took
a few seconds longer to activate.
But at that distance,
I knew you would try
to dodge my attack if I
made a show of getting
into my majestic pose.
Whoa, can you believe it?
Double the golden hour?
That means Yachihou must have frozen
time for an entire ten seconds!
But how were you able...
A genius such as I only gets
more brilliant over time.
Not including that in your
calculations was your downfall.
To be
continued
Command!
Well, he might be all right.
It ain't over yet! Stand up!
Now's the time to show him what
the seven squadrons made of!
Hang in there!
Let's go!
You got it!
When her learning ability acquires
another that comes with a cost attached,
she can't execute a skill
switch until the price is paid.
That's why she can't just
change abilities mid-match.
You need to think back to the past.
You were never up to snuff when
it was something important.
This time is no different.
You don't have a way
to counter prime time.
Just give up and concede.
Is it happening again?
Were all my efforts in vain?
Hey, you know she's trying
to psych us out. Right?
Yuki, look at your sister's face.
That ability took a toll on her.
She's exhausted.
She probably can't use it again.
Quitting when we're this close to victory?
I'd be ashamed if My master
did something that stupid.
You're clearly running
out of steam as well.
And you've got a A smart
mouth for a damn slave.
I'll punish you when this is over!
She's up!
It looked like the end of the line for
Himari, but she's back on her feet again!
Could we be approaching
the grand finale at last?
Oh, hell yeah!
Aw, she managed to stand up.
No more of this shameful behavior.
You don't want to
embarrass your commander.
I could easily freeze time again and
staying strong and fighting to the finish.
It's never considered shameful
for the seventh squadron.
I thought breaking your spirit now
would make it easy to train her later,
but do what we practice. You got it.
Golden hour.
I can't see, but I already struck a pulse!
Breathe for five seconds!
It's time to end this!
What?
I can't see Himari!
I had no idea that you were so desperate.
Can it be?
It's all over!
Himari Azuma is the winner!
That's one point for the seventh squadron!
They used the flash and smoke from Yuki's
reverse transformation to blind her.
Not bad.
You two really did your research.
My goodness!
Poor Yachiho lost the match!
Let's think of it as an opportunity
to learn from her mistakes.
Yuki! Still down!
There's no need to worry.
Did we... beat her?
Yeah, but you lost consciousness
after getting shot.
Ordinarily, injuries like these
would be life-threatening.
But since you've sustained them inside my
barrier, they'll heal up as good as new.
There!
You're all clear to move around freely!
That's amazing!
It's already gone!
Get off!
She said you're back to normal.
You've got no excuse to lean on me.
Hey, you don't have to be so rough.
I was unconscious until 30 seconds ago.
We actually did it.
Now that I can relax,
I feel really thirsty.
Well, you did do a lot of running.
Our timing on that one was
absolutely perfect i know right
I remember you catching a nasty cold right
before entrance exams because you worked
Yourself too hard i thought you were an
overachiever and you were pretty naive but
Let's go get something to drink
I worked up a thirst, too.
Hold it right there!
You've gotten a lot stronger.
I'll admit that.
I'll treat you better from now on.
Are you ready to join
the Azuma family again?
Come back home with me, Himari?
Yachiho
The 7th Squadron Is my home now?
There's nothing you could say
To convince me to go back!
Come on, let's get out of
here Yeah Oh my goodness!
Poor Yachiho She's just got an
unconventional way of expressing her love.
Come on, let's go get you changed.
There, there.
You don't need to cry.
Finally.
Huh?
What was that?
Was that my reward?
I guess it's starting.
Let's go over the first match.
Pay attention, Yachi-ho.
I have been told this was the little
slave's first fight against a human.
He knew your wounds would heal,
but there's a chance he subconsciously
put the brakes on his attacks.
If that's true, then the first direct
hit would have killed you instantly.
Something to consider in the future.
That's not all either.
After primetime,
it was foolish to allow your opponent a
reprieve instead of finishing her off.
Never underestimate the enemy.
Okay, I understand.
Now about that boy,
the way he kept pushing and using
himself as a decoy at the last second.
That's a slave, like no other.
Imari's taking a long time.
Should I check on her and Mr. Yuki?
Oh, I wouldn't mind getting them!
I worked up quite a thirst after
all that cheering that we did.
Your match starts soon.
Be careful not to drink too much water.
Copy that!
Himari pulled out all the stops.
I want to try and impress
Yuki with my skills, too.
Because of you?
I was able to beat her.
I couldn't have done it without you.
I appreciate it.
Himari.
I want you to know that I'm not just
saying that as part of your reward.
I really mean it!
What was that?!
It wasn't my choice!
I was forced to do it!
I thought that was obvious!
I swear to God, your reward is so obscene!
Himari's got a sharp tongue.
But her lips.
Her lips are unbelievably soft.
Wait, hold on?
Are you sure about not going back home?
Positive
The commander helped me out in tough
times I'll never leave her side
Look
Look.
I know I've been kind of cruel to you.
I'm sorry.
Maybe boys aren't so bad.
Thanks a lot, Miss Himari.
Can you chop the miss?
Given the circumstances, it feels weird.
But kissing is the price of
the ability and nothing more,
so don't get the wrong idea.
I am fully aware of that!
So that's what she meant
by physically demanding?
I'm sorry, Sahara, for losing my match.
It's up to you to win.
Sahara?
Hey, wake up!
The next round is starting soon!
What the hell, Sahara? Sahara!
Sahara?
How do you feel?
I got this just like I always do!
I'll never forget that you are
ready to set another whirl.
My heart is against each other.
I will never forget
that I'll never forget.
Next - , then, I will never leave it.
Next - , I will never leave it.
I will not delete it.
Thank you.
I will not let you start.
My strength is chasing me, I
will not let you know where I am?
but I will not let you start.
I will never let you
know
where your time is.
Kama-sama, Iyo.
Ahem, please excuse her.
Next time, let's how to twinkle.